export const QUESTIONS_LIST = [
  {
    id:0,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"One Does Not Simply Walk Into Mordor."',
        answer: 'Lord of the Rings'
      },
      {
        question: 'When Gondor called for aid who was it that answered the call?',
        answer: 'Rohan'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who was there three thousand years ago, the day the strength of Men failed?',
        answer: 'Elrond'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:1,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"Come quick. They\'ve gone wild. The girls have gone wild."',
        answer: 'Mean Girls'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who coined the term fetch?',
        answer: 'Gretchen Wieners'
      },
      {
        question: 'What did Gretchen Wieners father invent?',
        answer: 'The Toaster Strudel'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:2,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"It can\'t be reasoned with. It doesn\'t feel pity, or remorse, or fear. And it absolutely will not stop... ever, until you are dead!"',
        answer: 'Terminator'
      },
      {
        question: 'In Terminator 2, Rober Patrick plays the antagonist Terminator who\'s primary goal is to kill John Connor. What model Terminator does he play?',
        answer: 'T-1000'
      },
      {
        question: 'What was the name of the artificial intelligence that initiates Judgment Day and wages the Future War?',
        answer: 'SkyNet'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:3,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his Liver With Some Fava Beans And A Nice Chianti."',
        answer: 'The Silence of the Lambs'
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of Buffalo Bills dog?',
        answer: 'Precious'
      },
      {
        question: 'What Q Lazzarus song is Buffalo Bill listenting to when he puts on his skin suit?',
        answer: 'Goodbye Horses'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:4,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"I\' sorry I ruined your black panther party."',
        answer: 'Forest Gump'
      },
      {
        question: 'Forest may not be a smart man but he does in fact know what this is. What is it?',
        answer: 'Love'
      },
      {
        question: 'As a result of drinking what Forest estimated to be about 15 of these, Forest told JFK he had to pee. What did Forest drink?',
        answer: 'Dr Pepper'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"I\'ve seen things you people wouldn\'t believe. Attack ships on fire off the shoulder of Orion. I watched C-beams glitter in the dark near the Tannh√§user Gate. All those moments will be lost in time, like tears in rain."',
        answer: 'Blade Runner'
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the name of the company that designs and builds the replicants? Note the company is also present in the Alien universe.',
        answer: 'Tyrell Coorporation'
      },
      {
        question: 'In what US city does Blade Runner take place in?',
        answer: 'Los Angeles'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:6,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"Here, if you have a milkshake, and I have a milkshake, and I have a straw. There it is, it\'s a straw, you see? Watch it. Now my straw reaches across the room and starts to drink your milkshake. I... drink... your... milkshake. I drink it up!"',
        answer: 'There Will Be Blood'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who directed there will be blood?',
        answer: 'Paul Thomas Anderson'
      },
      {
        question: 'question',
        answer: 'answer'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:7,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"And I guess that was your accomplice in the wood chipper."',
        answer: 'Fargo'
      },
      {
        question: 'How did the prostitutes describe Steve Buscemis character when questioned by Marge?',
        answer: 'Funny Looking'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who Directed Fargo?',
        answer: 'Ethan Coen'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:8,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"What\'s the most you ever lost on a coin toss?"',
        answer: 'No Country for Old Men'
      },
      {
        question: 'Upon winning the coin toss where does the gas station proprieter attempt to place the coin, before being told not to?',
        answer: 'His pocket'
      },
      {
        question: 'When describing the man he is hired to track, Woody Harrelsons character Carson says "He\'s bad enough that you called me. He\'s a psychopathic killer, but so what? There\'s plenty of them around" Who is he describing? First or last name is fine.',
        answer: 'Anton Chigurh'
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    id:9,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>"Our pets heads are falling off!"',
        answer: 'Dumb and Dumber'
      },
      {
        question: 'What color tuxedo does Lloyd wear to the International Preservation Society event?',
        answer: 'Orange'
      },
      {
        question: 'What is Lloyds last name?',
        answer: 'Christmas'
      },
    ]
  },
  // {
  //   id:9,
  //   questions: [
  //     {
  //       question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>""',
  //       answer: 'answer'
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: 'question',
  //       answer: 'answer'
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: 'question',
  //       answer: 'answer'
  //     },
  //   ]
  // },
  // {
  //   id:9,
  //   questions: [
  //     {
  //       question: 'What flick is this quote from?<br>""',
  //       answer: 'Fargo'
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: 'How',
  //       answer: 'Funny'
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: 'Who',
  //       answer: 'Ethan'
  //     },
  //   ]
  // },
]